Genetics Society of America Records 1921-1982 Mss.575.06.G28p
American Philosophical Society
- Genetics Society of America Records, 1921-1984; 24.5 Linear feet 24.5 lin. feet
  - Records, 1956 (Box 14)
    - Dover Publications, 1956 (Box 14)
    - Dunn, Leslie C, 1956 (Box 14)
    - Emsweller, S L, 1956 (Box 14)
    - Faverge, A C, 1956 (Box 14)
    - Fox, Allen S, 1956 (Box 14)
    - Fraser, Donald A, 1956 (Box 14)
    - Fraser, F Clark, 1956; 2 folders (Box 14)
      - Fraser, F Clark, 1956 (Box 14)
      - Committee on Genetic Effects of Radiation, 1956 (Box 14)
    - Fuerst, Robert, 1956 (Box 14)
    - Fuscaldo, K, 1956 (Box 14)
    - Genetics, 1956 (Box 14)
    - Giles, Norman H, 1956 (Box 14)
    - Goodrich, H B, 1956 (Box 14)
    - Gots, Joseph S, 1956 (Box 14)
    - Gowen, John W, 1956 (Box 14)
    - Grant, Verne, 1956 (Box 14)
    - Genetics Society of America, 1956; 19 folders (Box 14)
      - Ballot, 1956 (Box 14)
      - Biographical Sketch, 1956 (Box 14)
      - Executive Committee, 1956 (Box 14)
      - Genetics Literature Requests, 1956 (Box 14)
      - Meetings, 1956 (Box 14)
      - Membership Records, 1956; 6 folders (Box 14)
      - Newsletters, 1956 (Box 14)
      - Public Education & Scientific Freedom Committee, 1956 (Box 14)
      - Records of the GSA. no. 25, 1955 1956 (Box 14)
      - Secretary's letter to Committee Chairmen, 1956 (Box 14)
      - Secretary's Notes, 1956 (Box 14)
      - Sustaining Membership Committee, 1956 (Box 14)
      - Storrs Meeting - Call for papers, 1956 (Box 14)
      - Storrs Meeting - Program, 1956 (Box 14)
    - Hersh, Amos Henry - Biography, 1956 (Box 14)
    - Kaufmann, Berwind P, 1956 (Box 14)
    - Kelly, J P, 1956 (Box 14)
    - Kimball, R F, 1956 (Box 14)
    - Landauer, Walter, 1956 (Box 14)
    - Laughnan, John R, 1956 (Box 14)
    - Lee, William R, Jr., 1956 (Box 14)
    - Levitan, Max, 1956 (Box 14)
    - Lieb, Margaret, 1956 (Box 14)
    - Lush, J L, 1956 (Box 14)
    - MacMillan Co., 1956 (Box 15)
    - McPhee, Hugh C, 1956 (Box 15)
    - Mangelsdorf, Paul C, 1956 (Box 15)
    - Marshak, Alfred, 1956 (Box 15)
    - Medical College of Virginia, 1956 (Box 15)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1956; 2 folders (Box 15)
    - Murphy, R P, 1956 (Box 15)
    - Nanney, David L, 1956 (Box 15)
    - National Academy of Sciences, 1956 (Box 15)
    - National Research Council, 1956 (Box 15)
    - Oliver, Clarence P., 1956; 2 folders (Box 15)
    - Owen, Ray D., 1956 (Box 15)
    - Philosophical Library, New York, 1956 (Box 15)
    - Plough, H H, 1956 (Box 15)
    - Powers, E. L., 1956 (Box 15)
    - Quiring, D. P., 1956 (Box 15)
    - Rhoades, M. M., 1956 (Box 15)
    - Ribicoff, Abraham, 1956 (Box 15)
      Governor of Connecticut
    - Rugh, Roberts, 1956 (Box 15)
    - Russell, E. S., 1956 (Box 15)
    - Ryan, Francis J., 1956 (Box 15)
    - Sachs, Leo, 1956 (Box 15)
    - Sax, Karl, 1956 (Box 15)
    - Schultz, Jack, 1956 (Box 15)
    - Science, 1956 (Box 15)
    - Science Museum Library, London, 1956 (Box 15)
    - Sears, E. R., 1956 (Box 15)
    - Shaw, Richard F., 1956 (Box 15)
    - Singleton, W. Ralph, 1956; 5 folders (Box 15)
    - Snyder, Lawrence H., 1956 (Box 15)
    - Sonneborn, Tracy M., 1956 (Box 15)
    - Sparrow, Arnold H., 1956 (Box 15)
    - Spencer, Warren P., 1956 (Box 15)
    - Spillman, Ramsay, 1956 (Box 15)
    - Stormont, Clyde, 1956 (Box 15)
    - Strauss, Bernard S., 1956 (Box 15)
    - Swanson, C. P., 1956 (Box 15)
    - Tenth International Congress on Genetics, 1956 (Box 15)
    - Tinker, A. Harriet, 1956 (Box 15)
    - Waddington, C. H., 1956 (Box 15)
    - Wagner, Robert, 1956 (Box 15)
    - Wallace, Bruce, 1956 (Box 15)
    - Wang, Chi-Wu, 1956 (Box 15)
    - Waverly Press, 1956 (Box 15)
    - Weinstein, Alexander, 1956 (Box 15)
    - Wellwood, Arnold A., 1956 (Box 15)
    - Wentworth, Edward N., 1956 (Box 15)
    - Whiting, Anna R, 1956 (Box 15)
    - Witkin, Evelyn M, 1956 (Box 15)
  - Records, 1957 (Box 15)
    - Abegg, F A, 1957 (Box 15)
    - American Academy of Microbiology, 1957 (Box 15)
    - American Association for the Advancement of Science, 1957 (Box 15)
    - American Institute of Biological Sciences, 1957 (Box 15)
    - American Society of Zoologists, 1957 (Box 15)
    - Bacharach, M M, 1957 (Box 15)
    - Baker, W K, 1957 (Box 15)
    - Bartlett, Harvey H, 1957 (Box 15)
    - Biological Institute of Belgrade, 1957 (Box 15)
    - Bora, K C, 1957 (Box 15)
    - Botanical Society of America, 1957 (Box 15)
    - Boyes, J W, 1957 (Box 15)
    - Braun, Werner, 1957 (Box 15)
    - Brauer, Gerald, 1957 (Box 15)
    - Brink, R A, 1957; 2 folders (Box 15)
    - Chittle, Clarence, 1957 (Box 15)
    - Chi-Wu, Wang, 1957 (Box 15)
    - Cleland, Ralph E, 1957 (Box 15)
    - Conger, Alan D, 1957 (Box 15)
    - Copeland, D Eugene, 1957 (Box 15)
    - Craig, George B, 1957 (Box 15)
    - Crow, James F, 1957 (Box 15)
    - Cuany, Robin L, 1957 (Box 15)
    - Davis, Mrs. Bradley M, 1957 (Box 15)
    - Dempster, E R, 1957 (Box 15)
    - Dunn, Leslie C, 1957 (Box 15)
    - Fraser, Clarke F, 1957 (Box 15)
    - Genetics Society of Japan, 1957 (Box 15)
    - Giles, N H, 1957 (Box 15)
    - Glass, H Bentley, 1957 (Box 15)
    - Glassman, Edward, 1957 (Box 15)
    - Goodspeed, Dr. T H, 1957 (Box 15)
    - Goodwin, K, 1957 (Box 15)
    - Gowen, John W, 1957 (Box 15)
    - Genetics Society of America, 1957; 22 folders (Box 15)
      - Ballot, 1957 (Box 15)
      - Business Meeting, Agenda, 1957 (Box 15)
      - Committee Chairmen, 1957 (Box 15)
      - Executive Committee, 1957; 2 folders (Box 15)
      - Members - Deceased, 1957 (Box 15)
      - Membership Nominations, 1957 (Box 15)
      - Membership Records (Folders 1-5), 1957; 5 folders (Box 15)
      - Membership Records (Folders 6-9), 1957; 4 folders (Box 16)
      - Newsletters, 1957 (Box 16)
      - Nominating Committee, 1957 (Box 16)
      - Program, 1957 (Box 16)
      - Program Committee, 1957 (Box 16)
      - Records, 1957 (Box 16)
      - Sustaining Membership Committee, 1957 (Box 16)
    - Harshbarger, Boyd, 1957 (Box 16)
    - Hartman, Philip E, 1957 (Box 16)
    - Hovin, Arne W, 1957 (Box 16)
    - Hutt, F B, 1957 (Box 16)
    - Kaeiser, Margaret, 1957 (Box 16)
    - Lambert, W V, 1957 (Box 16)
    - Lerner, Michael I, 1957 (Box 16)
    - Little, C C, 1957 (Box 16)
    - MacDowell, E Carleton, 1957 (Box 16)
    - Mangelsdorf, Paul C, 1957 (Box 16)
    - Marshak, Alfred, 1957 (Box 16)
    - Miller, W J, 1957 (Box 16)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1957 (Box 16)
    - Ninth International Botanical Congress, 1957 (Box 16)
    - Newby, W W, 1957 (Box 16)
    - Oakland, G B, 1957 (Box 16)
    - Oliver, C P, 1957 (Box 16)
    - Owen, Ray D, 1957; 2 folders (Box 16)
    - Payne, Fernandus, 1957 (Box 16)
    - Perkins, David, 1957 (Box 16)
    - Perry, Thomas O, 1957 (Box 16)
    - Peters, Walter, 1957 (Box 16)
    - Ray, David T, 1957 (Box 16)
    - Riddle, Oscar, 1957 (Box 16)
    - Rubin, B A, 1957 (Box 16)
    - Salamun, Peter J, 1957 (Box 16)
    - Satina, Sophie, 1957 (Box 16)
    - Savitsky, V F, 1957 (Box 16)
    - Searle, A G, 1957 (Box 16)
    - Serres, Frederick J de, 1957 (Box 16)
    - Singleton, W Ralph, 1957 (Box 16)
    - Sparr, Gladys, 1957 (Box 16)
    - Spencer, Herbert C, 1957 (Box 16)
    - Sprague, Lucian M, 1957 (Box 16)
    - Srb, Adrian M, 1957 (Box 16)
    - Stadler, Janice, 1957 (Box 16)
    - Sullivan, Robert L, 1957 (Box 16)
    - Swanson, C P, 1957 (Box 16)
    - Thayer, James H, 1957 (Box 16)
    - Tsunewaki, Koichiro, 1957 (Box 16)
    - Warren, Don C, 1957 (Box 16)
    - Waverly Press, Inc., 1957 (Box 16)
    - Wellwood, Arnold A, 1957 (Box 16)
    - Whiting, P W, 1957 (Box 16)
    - Yarborough, J M, 1957 (Box 16)
  - Records, 1958 (Box 16)
    - American Association for the Advancement of Science, 1958 (Box 16)
    - American Institute of Biological Sciences, 1958 (Box 16)
    - American Society of Zoologists, 1958 (Box 16)
    - Baker, William K, 1958 (Box 16)
    - Bora, K C, 1958 (Box 16)
    - Botanical Society of America, 1958 (Box 16)
    - Boyes, J W, 1958 (Box 16)
    - Brink, R A, 1958 (Box 16)
    - Carothers, E Eleanor, 1958 (Box 16)
    - Cleland, Ralph E, 1958 (Box 16)
    - Conger, Alan D, 1958 (Box 16)
    - Cooper, Kenneth, 1958 (Box 16)
    - Crow, James F, 1958 (Box 16)
    - Demerec, M, 1958 (Box 16)
    - Egolf, Donald R, 1958 (Box 16)
    - Emsweller, S L, 1958 (Box 16)
    - Fraser, F Clarke, 1958 (Box 16)
    - Gopal-Ayengar, A R, 1958 (Box 16)
    - Genetics Society of America, 1958; 17 folders (Box 17)
      - Membership Records, 1958; 11 folders (Box 17)
      - Newsletters, 1958 (Box 17)
      - Nominating Committee, 1958 (Box 17)
      - Officers, 1958 (Box 17)
      - Records, 1958; 2 folders (Box 17)
      - Sustaining Members, 1958 (Box 17)
    - Heston, W E, 1958 (Box 17)
    - Hutt, F B, 1958 (Box 17)
    - Katznelson, H, 1958 (Box 17)
    - Lederberg, Joshua, 1958 (Box 17)
    - Lerner, I M, 1958 (Box 17)
    - Mangelsdorf, P C, 1958 (Box 17)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1958; 2 folders (Box 17)
    - Mundkur, Balaji, 1958 (Box 17)
    - National Science Foundation, 1958 (Box 17)
    - New York Botanical Garden, 1958 (Box 17)
    - Oliver, C P, 1958; 2 folders (Box 17)
    - Owen, Ray D, 1958; 2 folders (Box 17)
    - Payne, Fernandus, 1958 (Box 17)
    - Quarterly Review of Biology, 1958 (Box 17)
    - Reinhard, Ed. George, 1958 (Box 17)
    - Report of American Institute of Biological Sciences Committee on Maintenance of Genetic Stocks, 1958 (Box 17)
    - Russell, W L, 1958 (Box 17)
    - Sager, Ruth, 1958 (Box 17)
    - Satina, Sophie, 1958 (Box 17)
    - Stern, Curt, 1958 (Box 17)
    - Swanson, C P, 1958 (Box 17)
    - Tenth International Congress on Genetics, 1958; 2 folders (Box 17)
    - U.S. Department of Health, Education and Welfare, 1958 (Box 17)
    - Wainwright, S D, 1958 (Box 17)
    - Whiting, P W, 1958 (Box 17)
  - Records, 1959 (Box 17)
    - American Association for the Advancement of Science, 1959 (Box 17)
    - American Institute of Biological Sciences, 1959; 2 folders (Box 17)
    - Comstock, Ralph E, 1959 (Box 18)
    - Emsweller, S L, 1959 (Box 18)
    - Genetics Society of America, 1959; 33 folders (Box 18)
      - Auditing Committee, 1959 (Box 18)
      - Ballot, 1959 (Box 18)
      - Career Information Requests, 1959 (Box 18)
      - Committee on Maintenance of Genetic Stocks, 1959 (Box 18)
      - Executive Committee, 1959 (Box 18)
      - Membership Records, 1959; 15 folders (Box 18)
      - Newsletters, 1959 (Box 18)
      - Nominating Committee, 1959 (Box 18)
      - Program Committee, 1959 (Box 18)
      - Program Correspondence, 1959; 2 folders (Box 18)
      - Records, 1959; 6 folders (Box 18)
      - Sustaining Membership Committee, 1959 (Box 18)
      - Treasurer's Report, 1959 (Box 18)
    - Landman, Otto E, 1959 (Box 18)
    - Lerner, I Michael, 1959 (Box 18)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1959 (Box 18)
    - Morgan, Walter, 1959 (Box 18)
    - National Science Foundation, 1959 (Box 18)
    - Newcombe, Howard B, 1959 (Box 18)
    - Oliver, Clarence P, 1959 (Box 18)
    - Owen, Ray D, 1959 (Box 18)
    - Pennsylvania State University Meeting, 1959 (Box 18)
    - Sax, Karl, 1959 (Box 18)
    - Sears, E R, 1959 (Box 18)
    - Swanson, Carl P, 1959 (Box 18)
    - Tenth International Congress on Genetics, 1959 (Box 18)
  - Records, 1960 (Box 19)
    - American Association for the Advancement of Science - Council, 1960 (Box 19)
    - American Institute of Biological Sciences, 1960; 2 folders (Box 19)
    - Boyes, J W, 1960 (Box 19)
    - Crow, James F, 1960 (Box 19)
    - Dunn, L C, 1960 (Box 19)
    - Genetics Society of America, 1960; 26 folders (Box 19)
      - Ballot, 1960 (Box 19)
      - Executive Committee, 1960 (Box 19)
      - Membership Records, 1960; 15 folders (Box 19)
      - Newsletters, 1960 (Box 19)
      - Nominating Committee, 1960 (Box 19)
      - Program Abstracts, 1960; 2 folders (Box 19)
      - Program Committee, 1960 (Box 19)
      - Records, 1960; 4 folders (Box 19)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1960 (Box 19)
    - Oklahoma State University Meeting, 1960 (Box 19)
    - Schwartz, Drew, 1960 (Box 19)
    - Swanson, C P, 1960 (Box 19)
  - Records, 1961 (Box 20)
    - American Association for the Advancement of Science - Council, 1961 (Box 20)
    - American Institute of Biological Sciences, 1961 (Box 20)
    - American Society of Zoologists, 1961 (Box 20)
    - Gowen, John W, 1961 (Box 20)
    - Genetics Society of America, 1961; 30 folders (Box 20)
      - Committee on Maintenance of Genetic Stocks, 1961 (Box 20)
      - Local Representatives, Purdue University Meeting, 1961; 2 folders (Box 20)
      - Membership Records, 1961; 13 folders (Box 20)
      - Newsletters, 1961 (Box 20)
      - Nominating Committee, 1961 (Box 20)
      - Program, 1961; 4 folders (Box 20)
      - Program Committee, 1961 (Box 20)
      - Records, 1961; 4 folders (Box 20)
      - Sustaining Membership Committeee, 1961 (Box 20)
      - Treasurer's Correspondence, 1961 (Box 20)
      - Treasurer's Records, 1961 (Box 20)
    - Hutt, F B, 1961 (Box 20)
    - Kaufmann, Berwind P, 1961 (Box 20)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1961 (Box 20)
    - National REsearch Council - Division of Biology & Agriculture, 1961 (Box 20)
    - Radiation Research Society, 1961 (Box 20)
    - Rajhathy, T, 1961 (Box 20)
    - Sax, Karl, 1961 (Box 20)
    - Sumption, Lavon J, 1961 (Box 20)
  - Records, 1962 (Box 21)
    - American Institute of Biological Sciences, 1962; 3 folders (Box 21)
    - Brink, R A, 1962 (Box 21)
    - Cohn, Norman S, 1962 (Box 21)
    - Crow, James F, 1962 (Box 21)
    - Dunn, G M, 1962 (Box 21)
    - Eleventh International Congress of Genetics (The Hague), 1962; 4 folders (Box 21)
    - Genetics, 1962; 5 folders (Box 21)
    - Genetics - Correspondence with David Perkins, 1962 (Box 21)
    - Gowen, John W, 1962 (Box 21)
    - Genetics Society of America, 1962; 38 folders (Box 21)
      - Auditing Committee, 1962 (Box 21)
      - Annual Meeting, 1962; 5 folders (Box 21)
      - Articles of Incorporation, 1962 (Box 21)
      - Committee on Maintenance of Genetic Stocks, 1962 (Box 21)
      - Council of the American Association for the Advancement of Science, 1962 (Box 21)
      - Executive Committee, 1962; 4 folders (Box 21)
      - Local Representatives, 1962 (Box 21)
      - Membership Records, 1962; 18 folders (Box 21)
        - Membership Records, 1962; 9 folders (Box 21)
        - Emeritus, 1962; 7 folders (Box 21)
        - New Members, 1962; 2 folders (Box 21)
      - Nominating Committee, 1962 (Box 21)
      - Sustaining Membership Committee, 1962 (Box 21)
      - Treasurer's Records, 1962; 4 folders (Box 22)
    - Hackel, Emanuel, 1962 (Box 22)
    - Intersociety Council of Animal Biology, 1962 (Box 22)
    - Kaufmann, Berwind P, 1962 (Box 22)
    - Lewis, E B, 1962 (Box 22)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1962 (Box 22)
    - Morgan, W E, 1962 (Box 22)
    - National Academy of Sciences, 1962 (Box 22)
    - National Committee on Radiation Protection and Measurement, 1962 (Box 22)
    - National Research Council - Division of Biology & Agriculture, 1962 (Box 22)
    - National Science Foundation, 1962 (Box 22)
    - Oceanographic Institute, 1962 (Box 22)
    - Oliver, Clarence P, 1962 (Box 22)
    - Owen, Ray D, 1962 (Box 22)
    - Peterson, P A, 1962 (Box 22)
    - Quarterly Review of Biology, 1962 (Box 22)
    - Reed, T Edward, 1962 (Box 22)
    - Russell, William, 1962 (Box 22)
    - Schwartz, D, 1962 (Box 22)
    - Sokoloff, Alexander, 1962 (Box 22)
    - Stern, Curt, 1962 (Box 22)
    - Tokuhata, George K, 1962 (Box 22)
  - Records, 1963 (Box 22)
    - American Association of Petroleum Geologists, 1963 (Box 22)
    - American Institute of Biological Sciences, 1963; 3 folders (Box 22)
    - American Philosophical Society, 1963 (Box 22)
    - Atomic Energy Commission, 1963 (Box 22)
    - Brown, Douglas F, 1963 (Box 22)
    - Buck, George E, 1963 (Box 22)
    - Budinger, Fred E Jr., 1963 (Box 22)
    - Cleland, Ralph E, 1963 (Box 22)
    - Comstock, R E, 1963 (Box 22)
    - Eleventh International Congress of Genetics, 1963; 4 folders (Box 22)
    - Genetics, 1963; 8 folders (Box 22)
    - Genetics - Correspondence with David Perkins, 1963; 4 folders (Box 22)
    - Genetics Society of America, 1963; 43 folders (Box 22)
      - Annual Meeting, Amherst Mass., 1963; 6 folders (Box 22)
        - Annual Meeting, Amherst Mass., 1963; 4 folders (Box 22)
        - Local Representative, 1963 (Box 22)
        - Minutes, 1963 (Box 22)
      - Auditing Committee, 1963 (Box 22)
      - Ballot, 1963 (Box 22)
      - Board of Directors - Minutes, 1963 (Box 22)
      - Campbell Award Committee, 1963 (Box 22)
      - Committee on Maintenance of Genetic Stocks, 1963 (Box 22)
      - Executive Committee, 1963; 3 folders (Box 22)
      - Form Letters, 1963 (Box 22)
      - Information Requests, 1963 (Box 23)
      - Membership Records, 1963; 10 folders (Box 23)
      - Newsletters, 1963 (Box 23)
      - Nominating Committee, 1963 (Box 23)
      - Program Committee, 1963 (Box 23)
      - RECORD Abstracts, 1963; 3 folders (Box 23)
      - Sustaining Membership, 1963 (Box 23)
      - Sustaining Membership Committee, 1963; 2 folders (Box 23)
      - Treasurer's Records, 1963; 7 folders (Box 23)
      - Treasurer's Report, 1963 (Box 23)
    - Hackel, Emanuel, 1963 (Box 23)
    - Hafner Publishing Co., 1963 (Box 23)
    - International Committee on Genetics Congresses, 1963 (Box 23)
    - Ives, Philip, 1963 (Box 23)
    - MacFarlane, E W, 1963 (Box 23)
    - Mayr, Ernst, 1963 (Box 23)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1963 (Box 23)
    - Murphy, R P, 1963 (Box 23)
    - National Committee on Radiation Protection and Measurements, 1963 (Box 23)
    - National REsearch Council - Division of Biology & Agriculture National Science Foundation, 1963 (Box 23)
    - Owen, Ray D, 1963 (Box 23)
    - Schultz, Jack, 1963 (Box 23)
    - U.S.Agency for International Development, 1963 (Box 23)
    - John Wiley & Sons, 1963 (Box 23)
  - Records, 1964 (Box 23)
    - American Institute of Biological Sciences, 1964 (Box 23)
    - Bonner, David M, 1964 (Box 23)
    - Boyes, J W, 1964 (Box 23)
    - Burnham, Charles R, 1964 (Box 23)
    - Chatterjee, Nando K, 1964 (Box 23)
    - Emerson, Sterling, 1964 (Box 23)
    - Genetics, 1964; 4 folders (Box 23)
    - Genetics Society of America, 1964; 31 folders (Box 23)
      - Annual Meeting, 1964; 3 folders (Box 23)
      - Annual Meeting - Minutes, 1964 (Box 24)
      - Annual Meeting - Program, 1964; 2 folders (Box 24)
      - Ballots, 1964 (Box 24)
      - Board of Directors, 1964 (Box 24)
      - Committees, 1964 (Box 24)
      - Constitution and By-Laws, 1964 (Box 24)
      - Information Requests, 1964; 2 folders (Box 24)
      - Membership Records, 1964; 6 folders (Box 24)
      - Mendel Centennial Committee, 1964; 3 folders (Box 24)
      - Nominating Committee, 1964 (Box 24)
      - Notes for Incoming Secretary, 1964 (Box 24)
      - RECORD - Abstracts, 1964; 4 folders (Box 24)
      - Sustaining Membership Committee, 1964; 2 folders (Box 24)
      - Tax Status, 1964 (Box 24)
      - Treasurer's Records, 1964 (Box 24)
    - Indian Society of Genetics and Plant Breeding, 1964 (Box 24)
    - Isenberg, F M, 1964 (Box 24)
    - Mendel Memorial Symposium, Czechoslovakia, 1964 (Box 24)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1964 (Box 24)
    - National Committee on Radiation Protection and Measurements, 1964 (Box 24)
    - National Research Council, 1964 (Box 24)
    - National Science Foundation, 1964 (Box 24)
    - Novitski, Edward, 1964 (Box 24)
    - Perkins, David D, 1964 (Box 24)
    - Plough, Harold, 1964 (Box 24)
    - Schultz, Jack, 1964 (Box 24)
    - Singleton, W Ralph, 1964 (Box 24)
    - Stubbe, Hans - Travel Grant, 1964 (Box 24)
    - Swanson, C P - Concerning Future of GSA Annual Meetings, 1964 (Box 24)
    - U.S. Department of H.E.W., 1964 (Box 24)
    - Wagner, Robert P, 1964 (Box 24)
  - Records, 1965 (Box 25)
    - American Association for Advancement of Science, 1965 (Box 25)
    - American Institute of Biological Sciences, 1965 (Box 25)
    - Brink, R A, 1965 (Box 25)
    - Caspari, Ernst, 1965 (Box 25)
    - Genetical Society, 1965 (Box 25)
    - Genetics, 1965 (Box 25)
    - Genetics Society of America, 1965; 12 folders (Box 25)
      - Announcements to Members, 1965 (Box 25)
      - Ballots, 1965 (Box 25)
      - Board of Directors, 1965 (Box 25)
      - Committee on Maintenance of Genetic Stocks, 1965 (Box 25)
      - Constitution & By-laws, 1965 (Box 25)
      - Contracts, 1965 (Box 25)
      - Genetics Careers Brochure, 1965 (Box 25)
      - Membership Records, 1965; 2 folders (Box 25)
      - Nominating Committee, 1965 (Box 25)
      - Sustaining Membership Committee, 1965 (Box 25)
      - Treasurer's Records, 1965 (Box 25)
    - Hoblitzelle National Award, 1965 (Box 25)
    - Kaufmann, Berwind P, 1965 (Box 25)
    - Mendel Centennial Conference, 1965 (Box 25)
    - Mendel Centennial Proceedings, 1965 (Box 25)
    - National Science FoundationNovitski, Edward, 1965 (Box 25)
    - Perkins, David D, 1965 (Box 25)
    - Pettus, David, 1965 (Box 25)
    - Rick, Charles M, 1965 (Box 25)
    - Russell, W L, 1965 (Box 25)
    - Twelth International Congress on Genetics - Tokyo, 1965 (Box 25)
    - Webb, Thomas, 1965 (Box 25)
  - Records, 1966 (Box 25)
    - American Institute of Biological Sciences, 1966 (Box 25)
    - Genetika (USSR), 1966 (Box 25)
    - Genetics, 1966 (Box 25)
    - Genetics Society of America, 1966; 15 folders (Box 25)
      - Annual Meeting, 1966 (Box 25)
      - Annual Meeting - Program, 1966; 3 folders (Box 25)
      - Auditing Committee, 1966 (Box 25)
      - Board of Directors, 1966 (Box 25)
      - Committee on the Maintenance of Genetic Stocks, 1966 (Box 25)
      - Membership Records, 1966; 4 folders (Box 25)
      - Obituaries, 1966 (Box 25)
      - Secretaty's Report, 1966 (Box 25)
      - Treasurer, 1966 (Box 25)
      - Treasurer's Report, 1966 (Box 25)
    - Hotchkiss, Rollin Douglas, 1966 (Box 25)
    - Mendel Centennial Proceedings, 1966 (Box 25)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1966 (Box 25)
    - National Research Council, 1966 (Box 25)
    - Report of Representative of the American Type Culture Collection, 1966 (Box 25)
    - Roman, Herschel, 1966 (Box 25)
    - Travelers Indemnity Company, 1966 (Box 25)
  - Records, 1967 (Box 26)
    - American Society for Horticultural Science, 1967 (Box 26)
    - Astavrov, B L, 1967 (Box 26)
    - Barratt, R W, 1967 (Box 26)
    - Bell, Whitfield Jenks, Jr., 1967 (Box 26)
    - Cohen, Barry M, 1967 (Box 26)
    - Eleventh International Botanical Congress - Seattle, 1967 (Box 26)
    - Genetics, 1967 (Box 26)
    - Genetics - Report of Editor, 1967 (Box 26)
    - Genetics Society of America, 1967; 9 folders (Box 26)
      - Annual Meeting, 1967 (Box 26)
      - Ballot, 1967 (Box 26)
      - Committee on Maintenance of Genetic Stocks, 1967 (Box 26)
      - Contracts, 1967 (Box 26)
      - Membership Records, 1967; 2 folders (Box 26)
      - Policy for Officers of the Society, 1967 (Box 26)
      - Sample work of the Secretary, 1967 (Box 26)
      - Treasurer's Records, 1967 (Box 26)
    - Lewis, E B, 1967 (Box 26)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1967 (Box 26)
    - Oliver, Clarence P, 1967 (Box 26)
    - Sparrow, Arnold H, 1967 (Box 26)
    - Strauss, B, 1967 (Box 26)
    - Wallace, Bruce, 1967 (Box 26)
  - Records, 1968 (Box 26)
    - American Institute of Biological Sciences, 1968 (Box 26)
    - Bell, Whitfield Jenks, Jr., 1968 (Box 26)
    - Entomological Society of America, 1968 (Box 26)
    - Genetics, 1968; 3 folders (Box 26)
    - Genetics Society of America, 1968; 27 folders (Box 26)
      - Abstracts, 1968; 2 folders (Box 26)
      - Annual Meeting, 1968 (Box 26)
      - Board of Directors, 1968; 2 folders (Box 26)